

Graphic Design + Marketing

Jenna Howard

- j.m.howard30@gmail.com
- Macon, GA
- jmhoward.design
- **&** (478) 719-0474

Profile

Graphic designer with +9 years of experience in digital & traditional marketing. Skilled at content creation, as well as branding & photography. Has a history with a range of clients including dentists, gas stations, hospitals, lawyers, restaurants, retail, & grocery stores.

Skills

- Active Campaign
 Facebook
- FIGMA
 Google
- IllustratorMailChimp
- Premiere ProPhotoshop

Employment

2020 - now Marketing Specialist at SPINEN

Translated ideas into concrete design for clients & internal staff. Developed promotional materials including brochures, clothing, manuals, .pdfs, pens, power points, signage, & social media posts. Managed social media pages & client interaction. Implemented digital ads that reached >30k people & newsletters that earned >\$30k in revenue.

2019 - now Graphic Designer at Freelance

Overhauled client branding & content planning. Constructed & maintained client web pages, Google Business pages, & social media accounts. Started mailing list for customer newsletters. Produced menus, photo shoots, & advertising for holiday catering. Reported client analytics.

2018 - 2019 Project Manager at Third Wave Digital

Administered projects for national & small business campaigns. Executed complex digital communications on behalf of key clients (e.g. 7-Eleven) including 3rd party vendors. Maintained a visual matrix of both content & format variations for menu boards across region, store types, & times of day for >200 stores.

Education

2011 - 2015 Georgia College & State University

Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication